https://ucoatit.com/privacy-policy/

1-800-826-2848ContactContact UsProduct CatalogRequest-a-Quote
MAIN WEBSITE
1-800-826-2848ContactContact UsProduct CatalogRequest-a-Quote
MAIN WEBSITE
SystemsProductsMarketsAutomotiveCommercialEducationFood IndustryGolfHospitalityIndustrialMunicipalRacingResidentialAboutBlogCompany HistoryCareersUCoat It NewsPhoto GalleryProject ProfilesUCoat It RacingProgramsFinancingContractor Program
MenuSystemsProductsMarketsAutomotiveCommercialEducationFood IndustryGolfHospitalityIndustrialMunicipalRacingResidentialAboutBlogCompany HistoryCareersUCoat It NewsPhoto GalleryProject ProfilesUCoat It RacingProgramsFinancingContractor Program
Search
ClosePrivacy PolicyShop Online / Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyLast updated: 7/31/2017UCoat It (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates https://www.ucoatit.com (the “Site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.Information Collection And UseWhile using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name (“Personal Information”).Log DataLike many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”).This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this data from time to time.CommunicationsWe may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that contain the information provide to us by you.CookiesCookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Changes To This Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy is effective as of 7/1/2017 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at 800-826-2848 or by email at contactus@ucoatit.com
Call us today at 800-826-2848Connect with us
Facebook-f
Youtube
Instagram
Linkedin-in
SystemsUCoatUCoat w/ UGlossUCoat w/ UGloss-AFUCoat w/ UFlekUCoat w/ UFlek-AFUltraLifeUClad-LVUGlazeMetallon 50Metallon 100Metallon 500MarketsAutomotiveCommercialEducationFood IndustryGolfHospitalityIndustrialMunicipalRacingResidentialAboutBlogsCompany HistoryCareersUCoat It NewsPhoto GalleryProject ProfilesUCoat It RacingProgramsFinancingContractor ProgramContactContact UsRequest-a QuoteHome | Systems | Products | Careers | UCoat It News | Photo Gallery | Project Profiles | Financing | Contractor Program | Contact Us | Request-a Quote | Shop OnlineYour privacy is important to us. Click here to view our Privacy Statement. All Images and content of this site copyright ©2020 UCI NA, LLC. All rights reserved.UCI NA, LLC is a privately owned company based in Royal Oak, MI, USA. All registered product names are exclusive property of UCI NA, LLC and may not be reproduced. This site is maintained by UCoat It. For sales or technical support call 1-800-826-2848.
